tests.com 2010-04-09

# PRIVACY POLICY | Tests.com

TESTS.COM considers privacy to be of the utmost importance. This policy explains how we use the personal information you submit. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. If you use TESTS.COM’s services, you agree to these terms.

#### What Information We Collect

We collect information provided by you when you register to use the site and when you submit an information request form or a contact inquiry form to us from our site.

#### What We Do with Collected Information

We use this information to communicate with you. We use your email address to send you messages about special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our service, respond to any problems that may arise and to gauge user trends to determine what part of our services are most popular with users.

Sometimes we will give you the opportunity to opt in to offers from third parties not affiliated with TESTS.COM. If you decide to accept these offers, we will provide, with your consent, your information to the third party. However, you should note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information users consent to give to third parties not affiliated with TESTS.COM. Any information users give to another party is governed by the rules of that party\s privacy policy, which may differ from this Privacy Policy. TESTS.COM is not responsible for information given to other parties. Please review their privacy policies prior to providing any information to third parties.

We may, at times, produce reports for advertisers containing aggregate information about our users such as demographic, age and online usage information. This allows us to work more closely with advertisers to provide content and offers that are most relevant to our users. We will never include any personal information of our users in these reports.

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information online (whether through TESTS.COM or any other service available online), personal or otherwise, that information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post personal information like your email online, you may receive unsolicited messages from others. TESTS.COM has no control over this use of your personal information.

#### Cookies

As you browse the TESTS.COM website, cookies are placed on your computer\s hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive.) Cookies allow us to track the areas of the site visited, and help us match your address and credit card information with your authentication so you don\t need to retype the information each time you visit our site.

We also use cookies to gather usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to our site and its various pages. Third parties may serve some of these cookies. We analyze this data to determine which parts of our site customers like and which parts need improvement. Automatically logged information is also used to analyze trends and to administer the site.

Cookies may also be placed on your computer by our vendors and affiliates, such as Google. TESTS.COM does not control these third party cookies and you should check the privacy policy of these third parties. You may be able to opt out of the use of cookies at the third party sites.

If you wish, you can adjust your web browser to block the use of cookies. We recommend that you set your browser to accept cookies to take full advantage of our website.

#### Usage Tracking

An IP address is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Internet so that your computer can be identified by the main computers, known as "web servers," that "serve up" web pages.

TESTS.COM and/or its affiliates collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregated information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When site users request pages from TESTS.COM and/or its affiliates\ sites, our servers log the site users\ IP addresses. We do not normally connect IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a site users\ session will be logged, but the site user will remain anonymous to us. The content management system logs error messages and security related events (such as users logging in and out). For anonymous users, this information is linked to IP address only. For users logged in, this information is linked to the users’ accounts, which may contain personally identifiable information. Also, any time a user enters information into a form on the site, the IP address of the user is recorded, and if the user is logged in, then the action is linked to that user account. Date, pages accessed, referring URL, and IP address are the information collected through tracking technologies. This information is used in aggregate (i.e. with personally identifiable information stripped out) to provide website utilization statistics to our advertisers and sponsors. The information is also used to provide services, to assist in customer service requests, to resolve errors, and to prevent security incursions against our site. In no case is the tracked personally identifiable information kept on the server for more than seven days, while the derived aggregate information is kept indefinitely. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a site user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site terms of use or terms of service or to protect our service, site, site users or others.

#### Disclosure

As a matter of policy and unless otherwise stated herein, TESTS.COM does not sell your personally identifiable information to other people or non-affiliated companies. However, we reserve the right to use your personally identifiable information to notify you of certain products and services about which you may have interest, and to investigate violations of the terms and provisions of this Policy or the Terms of Use. In addition, TESTS.COM aggregates personally identifiable information from its database and discloses non-personally identifiable elements to third parties for marketing, promotional and other commercial purposes.

When we contract with other companies to perform services (such as web hosting, credit card processing, user analysis, survey management), these companies may have access to your personally identifying information. By contractual agreement, these companies must treat your information in strict confidence, and not permit its sale, rental or disclosure to third parties. We will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies.

From time to time, we may partner with companies whose products we believe will interest our users. In conjunction with these partners, we may occasionally send promotional announcements to customers. To request that your name be excluded from these mailings with our marketing partners, simply send us a note indicating your preferences.

We also provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We do this so that we and our advertisers can understand you better, and so we can keep bringing you first-rate services. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, literal statements made by our members.

#### Security and Access

For transmitting your personal information to us, we use a secure server (SSL), which encrypts all of your personal information. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access.

You can access your registered information by clicking on My Account from every page on the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address and credit card information. Please note that you must be signed in to TESTS.COM to access this information.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as improvements become available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure with us, no data transmission over the Internet can be completely guaranteed as secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information in the Event of Merger or Asset Sale

TESTS.COM could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or all or substantially all of their respective assets could be acquired. Should such a combination, acquisition or transaction occur, you should expect that TESTS.COM will share some or all of your personally identifiable information with the acquiring or merged entity in order to continue serving you and others information, updates and offers concerning the websites.

#### Third Party Links

TESTS.COM does not monitor, control or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any third parties including, without limitation, any co-branded, partner or affiliated sites which are not owned or operated by TESTS.COM, or other third parties who may provide services through TESTS.COM. Please be aware that TESTS.COM site may contain links to other websites on the Internet and the services may be provided by such third parties. TESTS.COM assumes no liability or responsibility for the information collection and privacy practices of such third parties. Please consult each website\s privacy policy. In addition, TESTS.COM is not responsible for the content or data collection practices of any third party websites, including a third party\s use of cookies or other data-collection applications. Even though certain information collected by such third parties might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with their privacy practices and to contact them if you have any questions about their respective privacy policies and practices.

On behalf of various sponsors, TESTS.COM may provide sponsored links to third-party websites or resources ("Linked Sites"). TESTS.COM neither controls nor has reviewed or approved the content that appears on such Linked Sites. You acknowledge and agree that TESTS.COM is not responsible for the legality, accuracy or inappropriate nature of any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such Linked Sites. You further acknowledge and agree that TESTS.COM shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods and services available on or through any such Linked Site.

#### Visitors Outside the United States

TESTS.COM and the servers that make this site available worldwide are located in the United States. All matters relating to these sites are governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania in the United States. Any information you provide will be transferred to the United States. By visiting our sites and submitting information, you authorize this transfer.

#### Security

TESTS.COM uses secure server software (SSL) to process all website transactions. SSL encrypts information transmitted over the Internet, including personal data such as credit card number, name and address. TESTS.COM cannot warrant or guarantee the security of its servers, nor can it guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to TESTS.COM over the Internet. TESTS.COM places a priority on the security of personally identifiable information and we undertake reasonable security measures that comply with federal regulations to protect the data that resides on our servers.

TESTS.COM cannot definitively ensure that all of your personally identifiable information and communications will remain private and will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. Therefore, although we maintain and make every effort to comply with industry privacy standards, we do not promise, nor should you expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

#### Contact

If you have questions concerning your membership or this privacy policy, please contact our web administrator at [admin@tests.com](mailto:admin@tests.com).

Or you can contact us by mail at:

Tests.com LLC  
39 ½ E. Main Street  
Suite 7  
Ephrata, PA 17522

_Updated February_ _2010_
